DILAN LI

220 E Williams Ave, Salt Lake City, UT 84111
Phone: 801 686 7177 | Email: dilanli0706@gmail.com
Portfolio: https://dilanli.github.io/Profile-Website

GitHub: https://github.com/DilanLi

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/dilan-li-b3a8b3170

SUMMARY

Full Stack Developer with a background in Visual Arts and more than 4 years of experience in customer service. Creative thinker that enjoys finding efficient solutions and delivering intuitive user experiences. Motivated learner who is recognized by teammates for strong work ethic and attention to details. Fluent in Chinese.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Web Technologies & Frameworks: HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery, AJAX, BootStrap, React

Application/Web Server: Express Database and ORM: MySQL, MongoDB

Version Control and Deployment: GitHub, Heroku

Other: Bash, Chrome developer tools, Progressive Web Apps **Adobe Creative Suites**: Photoshop, Illustrator, Indesign

PROJECTS

Project Name: Lone Wolf

GitHub: https://github.com/corvus-cyber/LoneWolf **Deployed Link** https://lonewolfstrong.herokuapp.com

- Mobile first react application that allows users to watch exercise tutorials, create customized workouts, as well as to track their progress on a data dashboard.
- Established Express server and MongoDB database. Created a secure login system using Auth0.
 Formatted data to show dynamically on 4 different graphs using React-Vis.
- Tools used: MERN, Auth0, React-Vis

Project Name: Scout 19

GitHub: https://github.com/corvus-cyber/SCOUT19 **Deployed Link** https://corvus-cyber.github.io/SCOUT19

- Responsive web application that shows up-to-date Covid-19 counts on national and state levels. App includes a dynamic US map displaying colored state grades, and charts of positive tests rate in a history of 14 days.
- Researched on third party APIs to ensure data accountability and accuracy. Established AJAX calls to deliver dynamic data based on user input or user location. Generated data graphics and charts.
- Tools used: JavaScript, AJAX, third party APIs/ libraries

Project Name: Weather Dashboard

GitHub: https://github.com/DilanLi/Weather-Dashboard **Deployed Link** https://dilanli.github.io/Weather-Dashboard

- Weather app that delivers current day information as well as a 5 day forecast. Allows users to search for a city or uses their current location as a default.
- Created web layout using Bootstrap to ensure mobile responsiveness. Ensured the design for the interface is clean and intuitive. Using third party APIs to deliver dynamic weather data.
- Tools used: Bootstrap, CSS, JavaScript, AJAX

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp Certificate:

University of Utah, Salt Lake City, Utah May 2020 - Nov 2020

Bachelor of Fine Arts:

University of Utah, Salt Lake City, Utah Aug 2012 - May 2018

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelance Artist 2012 – Present

- Created paintings, illustrations, murals, installations, etc using design principles and artistic sensitivities
- Communicated with clients to meet their desired outcome within deadlines
- Worked individually and in group and flexibly adjusted in between
- Art have been featured in organizations such as Utah Museum of Contemporary Art, 15 Bytes Artists of Utah Magazine, Salt Lake Community College, etc

Registrar

Anna Zorina Gallery

2018 - 2019

- Assisted in art exhibitions in the aspects of communicating with artists, shipping companies and on site installation to ensure openings on time
- Worked within time frame for each exhibition and managed a variety of tasks based on deadlines
- Maintained gallery website and art work database and consistently paid attention to details

Server

Jinya Ramen Restaurant

2016 - 2018 & 2019 - 2020

- Delivered attentive customer service and received frequent positive feedback from customers
- Worked in fast paced environment during busy hours, coped well with stress while working with team members to ensure efficient table rotation

Travel Agent

Spring Tour Travel Service

2015 - 2016

- Planned tour itineraries, hotels, transportation, translators, etc for foreign tour groups and successfully accommodated more than 100 groups in peak season
- Frequently needed to solve problems to ensure smooth operation of large tours varying from 5-30 people